A Guide to the Institute of International Education records, Alumni and Historical Files, RG 1 FA1289
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Historical Files, 3
  - General - Britain Lists of P.L.584 Supervision only Grantees - 1952-53, 1953-54 (Reel 29, Side 1, Index 26), Reel 29, Side 1, Index 26 (Reel 29)
  - General - Bureau of Social Science Research - An Analysis of First Reports from Foreign Exchange Students (1951-52) - 1953 (Reel 27, Side 2, Index 3), Reel 27, Side 2, Index 3 (Reel 27)
  - General - Bureau of Social Science Research - Foreign Exchange Students Review Their Stay in the U.S. (Second Semester 1951-52) - 1953 (Reel 27, Side 2, Index 4), Reel 27, Side 2, Index 4 (Reel 27)
  - General - Department of State - An Orientation Study: The University Centers and Experiment in International Living Family Program Compared - 1953 (Reel 27, Side 2, Index 2), Reel 27, Side 2, Index 2 (Reel 27)
  - General - IIE Special Committee on Overseas Information Programs - Washington - Senator Hicken Looper - 1953 (Reel 28, Side 2, Index 16), Reel 28, Side 2, Index 16 (Reel 28)
  - General - Department of Information Educational Surveys - 1954-55 (Reel 27, Side 2, Index 1), Reel 27, Side 2, Index 1 (Reel 27)
  - General - Middleditch U.S. Students Abroad - Lists - 1955-56 (Reel 28, Side 1, Index 23), Reel 28, Side 1, Index 23 (Reel 28)
  - General - U.S. Abroad Program Miscellaneous Correspondence - 1957 (Reel 29, Side 1, Index 23), Reel 29, Side 1, Index 23 (Reel 29)
  - General - Clippings Valuable 1919-1922 (Reel 3, Side 1, Index 15), Reel 3, Side 1, Index 15 (Reel 3)
  - General - Publicity - Articles A. Palmer 1928 (Reel 18, Side 1, Index 19), Reel 18, Side 1, Index 19 (Reel 18)
  - General - Articles Published 1936 (Reel 5, Side 1, Index 22), Reel 5, Side 1, Index 22 (Reel 5)
  - General - Articles Published IIE 1937 (Reel 7, Side 2, Index 1), Reel 7, Side 2, Index 1 (Reel 7)
  - General - Correspondence Reguarding Books 1937 (Reel 7, Side 2, Index 12), Reel 7, Side 2, Index 12 (Reel 7)
  - General - Magazines 1937 (Reel 7, Side 2, Index 13), Reel 7, Side 2, Index 13 (Reel 7)
  - General - Correspondence Re: Books 1942 (Reel 12, Side 2, Index 24), Reel 12, Side 2, Index 24 (Reel 12)
  - Magazines 1942 (Reel 12, Side 2, Index 25), Reel 12, Side 2, Index 25 (Reel 12)
  - General - Counseling the Foreign Student 1943 (Reel 13, Side 1, Index 49), Reel 13, Side 1, Index 49 (Reel 13)
  - General Re Weaver of an International Ideal 1944 (Reel 13, Side 2, Index 12), Reel 13, Side 2, Index 12 (Reel 13)
  - General IIE - Washington Bureau Handbook of Fellowship and Scholarship Opportunities in the United States Open to Citizens of other American Republics 1944 (Reel 29, Side 1, Index 17), Reel 29, Side 1, Index 17 (Reel 29)
  - General Re Counseling the Foreign Student 1945 (Reel 14, Side 1, Index 27), Reel 14, Side 1, Index 27 (Reel 14)
  - General Re The German Problem: Education in Post-War Germany 1945 (Reel 14, Side 1, Index 28), Reel 14, Side 1, Index 28 (Reel 14)
  - General IIE Publications and Publicity 1948-1951 (Reel 17, Side 2, Index 9), Reel 17, Side 2, Index 9 (Reel 17)
  - General - Books and Pamphlets 1949 (Reel 19, Side 2, Index 11), Reel 19, Side 2, Index 11 (Reel 19)
  - General - Requests for Building Roads to Peace 1949 (Reel 19, Side 1, Index 6), Reel 19, Side 1, Index 6 (Reel 19)
  - General - Pamphlets 1950 (Reel 19, Side 1, Index 5), Reel 19, Side 1, Index 5 (Reel 19)
  - General Re: News Bulletin 1950 (Reel 19, Side 1, Index 7), Reel 19, Side 1, Index 7 (Reel 19)
  - General Re; Building Roads to Peace A-Z 1950 (Reel 19, Side 2, Index 1), Reel 19, Side 2, Index 1 (Reel 19)
  - General Re: Blueprint for Understanding A-K 1950 (Reel 19, Side 2, Index 2), Reel 19, Side 2, Index 2 (Reel 19)
  - General Re: Blueprint for Understanding L-R 1950 (Reel 19, Side 2, Index 3), Reel 19, Side 2, Index 3 (Reel 19)
  - General Re: Blueprint for Understanding S-Z 1950 (Reel 19, Side 2, Index 4), Reel 19, Side 2, Index 4 (Reel 19)
  - Germany Germanistic 1933 (Reel 4, Side 1, Index 46), Reel 4, Side 1, Index 46 (Reel 4)
  - Germany Germanistic 1935 Society (Reel 11, Side 2, Index 18), Reel 11, Side 2, Index 18 (Reel 11)
  - Germanistic Society of America 1944 (Reel 13, Side 1, Index 16), Reel 13, Side 1, Index 16 (Reel 13)
  - Stephen Duggan Germanistic Society of America General 1947 (Reel 15, Side 2, Index 16), Reel 15, Side 2, Index 16 (Reel 15)
  - Germanistic Society of America 1947 (Reel 15, Side 2, Index 20), Reel 15, Side 2, Index 20 (Reel 15)
  - Germany Germanistic Society of America Fellowship - Correspondence 1955-1960 (Reel 26, Side 2, Index 22), Reel 26, Side 2, Index 22 (Reel 26)
  - Germanistic Society of America Printed Forms 1928-1933 (Reel 7, Side 1, Index 3), Reel 7, Side 1, Index 3 (Reel 7)
  - Germany American German Student Exchange Incorporation, By-Laws, Minutes of Board Meetings 1921-1926 (Reel 7, Side 1, Index 15), Reel 7, Side 1, Index 15 (Reel 7)
  - Germany American German Student Exchange Publicity 1925-1940 (Reel 7, Side 1, Index 2), Reel 7, Side 1, Index 2 (Reel 7)
  - Germany American German Student Exchange Americans In Germany - Lists 1927-1934, 1935-1937, 1938-1939 (Reel 7, Side 1, Index 11), Reel 7, Side 1, Index 11 (Reel 7)
  - Germany American German Student Exchange Form Letters 1928-1939 (Reel 6, Side 2, Index 12), Reel 6, Side 2, Index 12 (Reel 6)
  - Germany American German Student Exchange Correspondence 1928-1939 (Reel 7, Side 1, Index 14), Reel 7, Side 1, Index 14 (Reel 7)
  - Germany American German Student Exchange Committee on Selection 1931-1935 (Reel 6, Side 2, Index 1), Reel 6, Side 2, Index 1 (Reel 6)
  - Germany American German Student Exchange Fellowships Offered 1932-1936 (Reel 6, Side 2, Index 18), Reel 6, Side 2, Index 18 (Reel 6)
  - Germany American German Student Exchange Correspondence 1929-1930 (Reel 7, Side 1, Index 21), Reel 7, Side 1, Index 21 (Reel 7)
  - Germany Akademische Austausch Dienst Printed Forms 1924-1931 (Reel 7, Side 1, Index 5), Reel 7, Side 1, Index 5 (Reel 7)
  - Germany American German Student Exchange Printed Forms 1929-1937 (Reel 7, Side 1, Index 1), Reel 7, Side 1, Index 1 (Reel 7)
  - Germany Deutcher Akademischer Austauschdienst Policies - Student Exchange Correspondence - 1930-1938 (Reel 26, Side 2, Index 15), Reel 26, Side 2, Index 15 (Reel 26)
  - Germany Correspondence with Dr. Morschbach 1929 (Reel 3, Side 1, Index 8), Reel 3, Side 1, Index 8 (Reel 3)
  - Germany Memos, Minutes, Copies of Important Letters - American -German Student Exchange 1929-1931 (Reel 6, Side 2, Index 27), Reel 6, Side 2, Index 27 (Reel 6)
  - Germany American German Student Exchange Miscellaneous Lists of Students 1929-1939 (Reel 7, Side 1, Index 16), Reel 7, Side 1, Index 16 (Reel 7)
  - Germany German Candidates for U.S. Fellowships Master Lists 1929-1940 (Reel 6, Side 2, Index 16), Reel 6, Side 2, Index 16 (Reel 6)
  - Germany Franz-Joseph Niemann 1930 (Reel 3, Side 2, Index 6), Reel 3, Side 2, Index 6 (Reel 3)
  - Special Projects Germany 1930-1931 William Blaschke (Reel 8, Side 1, Index 10), Reel 8, Side 1, Index 10 (Reel 8)
  - Special Projects Germany U-Z 1931 (Reel 8, Side 1, Index 11), Reel 8, Side 1, Index 11 (Reel 8)
  - Germany Von Humboldt - Stiftung Foreign Study Award Descirption 1931-1932, 1935 (Reel 26, Side 2, Index 26), Reel 26, Side 2, Index 26 (Reel 26)
  - Germany Comments on German Students Letters from Colleges and Universities 1931-1936 (Reel 6, Side 2, Index 21), Reel 6, Side 2, Index 21 (Reel 6)
  - Special Projects Germany R-Z 1932 (Reel 8, Side 1, Index 20), Reel 8, Side 1, Index 20 (Reel 8)
  - Germany Fellowships for German Students in U.S. 1932-1933, 1933-1934 (Reel 6, Side 2, Index 10), Reel 6, Side 2, Index 10 (Reel 6)
  - Extracts from Reports American Students in Germany 1932-1933, 1933-1934 (Reel 6, Side 1, Index 15), Reel 6, Side 1, Index 15 (Reel 6)
  - Germany Fellowships in Germany for Americans 1932-1934 (Reel 6, Side 2, Index 11), Reel 6, Side 2, Index 11 (Reel 6)
  - Germany Hamburg - Summer Courses 1932, 1936-1937 (Reel 6, Side 2, Index 26), Reel 6, Side 2, Index 26 (Reel 6)
  - American-German Student Exchange Memorandum to American Students Going Abroad 1932-1939 (Reel 6, Side 1, Index 16), Reel 6, Side 1, Index 16 (Reel 6)
  - Germany 1933 (Reel 4, Side 2, Index 9), Reel 4, Side 2, Index 9 (Reel 4)
  - Germany General 1933 (Reel 4, Side 1, Index 41), Reel 4, Side 1, Index 41 (Reel 4)
  - Germany A-Z 1933 (Reel 4, Side 1, Index 42), Reel 4, Side 1, Index 42 (Reel 4)
  - Germany General Junior Year Abroad (Reel 4, Side 1, Index 1), Reel 4, Side 1, Index 1 (Reel 4)
  - Germany 30 Percent Reduction 1933 (Reel 4, Side 2, Index 1), Reel 4, Side 2, Index 1 (Reel 4)
  - Germany Dr. A. Morsback 1933 (Reel 4, Side 2, Index 2), Reel 4, Side 2, Index 2 (Reel 4)
  - Germany - Letters RE: Treatment of Jews A-Z 1933-1934 (Reel 11, Side 1, Index 23), Reel 11, Side 1, Index 23 (Reel 11)
  - Germany Letter - Effects of Politics on German Universities 1934 Copies of Important Letters 1933-1934 (Reel 6, Side 2, Index 24), Reel 6, Side 2, Index 24 (Reel 6)
  - Germany Arrival of German Students for U.S. Conferences 1933-1939 (Reel 7, Side 1, Index 17), Reel 7, Side 1, Index 17 (Reel 7)
  - Germany General 1934 (Reel 11, Side 1, Index 22), Reel 11, Side 1, Index 22 (Reel 11)
  - Germany NAZI Propaganda File 1934 (Reel 10, Side 2, Index 5), Reel 10, Side 2, Index 5 (Reel 10)
  - Germany Re: NAZI Propaganda of Exchange Students in U.S. 1934 (Reel 17, Side 2, Index 13), Reel 17, Side 2, Index 13 (Reel 17)
  - Germany Jr. Year Abroad General 1934 (Reel 11, Side 1, Index 25), Reel 11, Side 1, Index 25 (Reel 11)
  - Germany Dr. A. Morsback 1934 (Reel 11, Side 1, Index 26), Reel 11, Side 1, Index 26 (Reel 11)
  - Germany Successful 1928-1929 1934 (Reel 10, Side 2, Index 45), Reel 10, Side 2, Index 45 (Reel 10)
  - Germany Successful 1928-1929 1934 (Reel 10, Side 2, Index 44), Reel 10, Side 2, Index 44 (Reel 10)
  - Germany Successful 1930-1931 1934 (Reel 10, Side 2, Index 43), Reel 10, Side 2, Index 43 (Reel 10)
  - Germany Successful 1931-1932 1934 (Reel 10, Side 2, Index 42), Reel 10, Side 2, Index 42 (Reel 10)
  - Germany Jr. Year Abroad Successful 1931-1932 1934 (Reel 10, Side 2, Index 47), Reel 10, Side 2, Index 47 (Reel 10)
  - Germany Fellowships for German Students in U.S. 1934-1935 (Reel 6, Side 2, Index 9), Reel 6, Side 2, Index 9 (Reel 6)
  - Germany American-German Students Exchange Awards 1934-1935 (Reel 6, Side 2, Index 15), Reel 6, Side 2, Index 15 (Reel 6)
  - Germany Professors of German - List 1934-1943 (Reel 6, Side 2, Index 14), Reel 6, Side 2, Index 14 (Reel 6)
  - Germany General 1935 (Reel 11, Side 2, Index 14), Reel 11, Side 2, Index 14 (Reel 11)
  - Germany A-Z 1935 (Reel 11, Side 2, Index 15), Reel 11, Side 2, Index 15 (Reel 11)
  - Germany A-M 1935 (Reel 11, Side 2, Index 8), Reel 11, Side 2, Index 8 (Reel 11)
  - Germany N-Z 1935 (Reel 11, Side 2, Index 9), Reel 11, Side 2, Index 9 (Reel 11)
  - Germany Jr. Year Abroad General 1935 (Reel 11, Side 2, Index 24), Reel 11, Side 2, Index 24 (Reel 11)
  - Germany German Exchange Students Alumni File 1935 (Reel 11, Side 2, Index 16), Reel 11, Side 2, Index 16 (Reel 11)
  - Germany Deutscher Akaemischer Austtauschdienst Von Fritsch 1935 (Reel 11, Side 2, Index 17), Reel 11, Side 2, Index 17 (Reel 11)
  - Germany Successful 1932-1933 1935 (Reel 10, Side 2, Index 41), Reel 10, Side 2, Index 41 (Reel 10)
  - Germany Fellowships for German Students in U.S. 1935-1936 (Reel 6, Side 2, Index 8), Reel 6, Side 2, Index 8 (Reel 6)
  - Germany American-German Student Exchange Committee on Selection 1935-1940 (Reel 6, Side 2, Index 2), Reel 6, Side 2, Index 2 (Reel 6)
  - Germany Americans to Germany - Lists, etc. 1935-1940 (Reel 7, Side 1, Index 6), Reel 7, Side 1, Index 6 (Reel 7)
  - Germany General 1936 (Reel 7, Side 1, Index 25), Reel 7, Side 1, Index 25 (Reel 7)
  - Germany General Junior Year Abroad 1936 (Reel 7, Side 1, Index 26), Reel 7, Side 1, Index 26 (Reel 7)
  - Special Projects Germany Plan B Prof. Herbert Kraus 1936 (Reel 8, Side 2, Index 20), Reel 8, Side 2, Index 20 (Reel 8)
  - Education Germany Heidelberg Anniversary Celebration 1936 (Reel 6, Side 1, Index 12), Reel 6, Side 1, Index 12 (Reel 6)
  - Germany Fellowships for German Studetns in the U.S. 1936-1937 (Reel 6, Side 2, Index 7), Reel 6, Side 2, Index 7 (Reel 6)
  - Germany U.S. Scholarships to University of Heidelberg 1936-1937 (Reel 7, Side 1, Index 12), Reel 7, Side 1, Index 12 (Reel 7)
  - Germany Criticisms of American German Student Exchange IIE Answers and Suggestions 1936-1938 (Reel 6, Side 2, Index 25), Reel 6, Side 2, Index 25 (Reel 6)
  - Germany Comments on German Students Letters from Colleges and Universities 1936-1938 (Reel 6, Side 2, Index 19), Reel 6, Side 2, Index 19 (Reel 6)
  - Germany American German Students Exchange Correspondence 1936-1940 (Reel 7, Side 1, Index 13), Reel 7, Side 1, Index 13 (Reel 7)
  - Germany Successful 1933-1934 1937 (Reel 10, Side 2, Index 40), Reel 10, Side 2, Index 40 (Reel 10)
  - Germany Successful 1934-1935 1937 (Reel 10, Side 2, Index 39), Reel 10, Side 2, Index 39 (Reel 10)
  - Germany Fellowships for German Students in U.S. 1937-1938 (Reel 6, Side 2, Index 6), Reel 6, Side 2, Index 6 (Reel 6)
  - Germany Information for Americans - Clothing, Accomodations, Reduced Travel Rates, Registered Marks 1937-1939 (Reel 7, Side 1, Index 8), Reel 7, Side 1, Index 8 (Reel 7)
  - Special Projects Germany A-Z 1938 (Reel 8, Side 2, Index 31), Reel 8, Side 2, Index 31 (Reel 8)
  - Special Projects Germany A-Z 1938 (Reel 8, Side 2, Index 32), Reel 8, Side 2, Index 32 (Reel 8)
  - Germany Successful 1935-1936 1938 (Reel 10, Side 2, Index 38), Reel 10, Side 2, Index 38 (Reel 10)
  - Germany Reports of Former U.S. Students in Germany - Extracts, Matriculation Papers 1938 (Reel 7, Side 1, Index 10), Reel 7, Side 1, Index 10 (Reel 7)
  - Germany Stipends for Americans - Memo, Humboldt, V.D.A. Heidelberg 1938 (Reel 7, Side 1, Index 7), Reel 7, Side 1, Index 7 (Reel 7)
  - Germany Comments on German Students Letters from Colleges and Universities 1938-1939 (Reel 6, Side 2, Index 20), Reel 6, Side 2, Index 20 (Reel 6)
  - Germany Fellowships for U.S. Born German 2nd Year Students. Fellowships for Germans in U.S. 1938-1939, 1940-1941 (Reel 6, Side 2, Index 4), Reel 6, Side 2, Index 4 (Reel 6)
  - Germany Replies to Dr. Duggan's Letter (May5, 1938) to 60 Colleges and Universities RE: German Student Propaganda and Scholastic Aptitude Group 1936-1937, 1938 (Reel 6, Side 2, Index 22), Reel 6, Side 2, Index 22 (Reel 6)
  - Germany Replies to Dr. Duggan Letter RE: German Students 1937-1938 Group 1938 (Reel 6, Side 2, Index 23), Reel 6, Side 2, Index 23 (Reel 6)
  - Germany Special Projects A-Z 1938-1939 (Reel 21, Side 1, Index 10), Reel 21, Side 1, Index 10 (Reel 21)
  - Germany Akademischer File RE Students-Scholars 1939 (Reel 10, Side 2, Index 2), Reel 10, Side 2, Index 2 (Reel 10)
  - Germany Correspondence RE Germany Today 1939 (Reel 9, Side 1, Index 7), Reel 9, Side 1, Index 7 (Reel 9)
  - Germany Rettig Files - On German Student Spies 1939-1940 (Reel 9, Side 1, Index 21), Reel 9, Side 1, Index 21 (Reel 9)
  - Germany Fellowships for German Students in U.S. 1939-1940 (Reel 6, Side 2, Index 5), Reel 6, Side 2, Index 5 (Reel 6)
  - Germany Special Projects A-Z 1940 (Reel 21, Side 1, Index 32), Reel 21, Side 1, Index 32 (Reel 21)
  - Germany 1942 (Reel 12, Side 1, Index 17), Reel 12, Side 1, Index 17 (Reel 12)
  - Germany Refugees 1942 (Reel 12, Side 1, Index 4), Reel 12, Side 1, Index 4 (Reel 12)
  - Germany Refugees 1942-1943 (Reel 16, Side 1, Index 16), Reel 16, Side 1, Index 16 (Reel 16)
  - Germany 1943 (Reel 13, Side 2, Index 31), Reel 13, Side 2, Index 31 (Reel 13)
  - Germany Refugee 1943 (Reel 13, Side 2, Index 32), Reel 13, Side 2, Index 32 (Reel 13)
  - Germany Refugees 1944 (Reel 16, Side 1, Index 17), Reel 16, Side 1, Index 17 (Reel 16)
  - Germany Office of Military Government (HICOG) Correspondence 1947-1948 (Reel 16, Side 2, Index 19), Reel 16, Side 2, Index 19 (Reel 16)
  - Germany Correspondence with War Department 1948-1949 (Reel 16, Side 2, Index 22), Reel 16, Side 2, Index 22 (Reel 16)
  - Germany List of Sponsors of German Students 1948-1949 (Reel 19, Side 1, Index 42), Reel 19, Side 1, Index 42 (Reel 19)
  - Germany Student Exchange Program 1948, 1950 (Reel 17, Side 1, Index 30), Reel 17, Side 1, Index 30 (Reel 17)
  - Germany A-Z 1949 (Reel 16, Side 2, Index 24), Reel 16, Side 2, Index 24 (Reel 16)
  - Germany 1949 (Reel 16, Side 2, Index 25), Reel 16, Side 2, Index 25 (Reel 16)
  - Germany Hospitality for Students 1949 (Reel 16, Side 2, Index 26), Reel 16, Side 2, Index 26 (Reel 16)
  - Germany Washington - Department of the Army General Staff 1949 (Reel 16, Side 2, Index 23), Reel 16, Side 2, Index 23 (Reel 16)
  - Germany Department of the Army Exchange Contract - Financial Details 1949-1950 (Reel 17, Side 2, Index 25), Reel 17, Side 2, Index 25 (Reel 17)
  - Germany Department of the Army Exchange Procedures and Publications 1949-1950 (Reel 17, Side 2, Index 26), Reel 17, Side 2, Index 26 (Reel 17)
  - Germany Advisory Committee for Occupied Areas 1949-1950 (Reel 19, Side 1, Index 29), Reel 19, Side 1, Index 29 (Reel 19)
  - Germany Office of US High Commissioner (HICOG) Correspondence 1949-1950 (Reel 16, Side 2, Index 20), Reel 16, Side 2, Index 20 (Reel 16)
  - Germany HICOG - Land Bremen 1949-1950 (Reel 19, Side 1, Index 31), Reel 19, Side 1, Index 31 (Reel 19)
  - Germany HICOG - Land Berlin 1949-1950 (Reel 19, Side 1, Index 32), Reel 19, Side 1, Index 32 (Reel 19)
  - Germany HICOG - Land Wuerttemberg - Baden 1949-1950 (Reel 19, Side 1, Index 36), Reel 19, Side 1, Index 36 (Reel 19)
  - Germany Lists RE Placement 1949-1950 (Reel 19, Side 1, Index 37), Reel 19, Side 1, Index 37 (Reel 19)
  - Germany Lists of German Applicants 1949-1950 (Reel 19, Side 1, Index 38), Reel 19, Side 1, Index 38 (Reel 19)
  - Germany HICOG - Land Bavaria 1949-1951 (Reel 19, Side 1, Index 33), Reel 19, Side 1, Index 33 (Reel 19)
  - Germany Office of US High Commissioner (HICOG) - Main Office Dr. Gunther 1949-1951 (Reel 16, Side 2, Index 21), Reel 16, Side 2, Index 21 (Reel 16)
  - Germany Deutscher Akaemischer Austtauschdienst Correspondence 1959-1960 (Reel 26, Side 2, Index 18), Reel 26, Side 2, Index 18 (Reel 26)
  - Germany Deutscher Akaemischer Austtauschdienst Correspondence 1960 (Reel 26, Side 2, Index 30), Reel 26, Side 2, Index 30 (Reel 26)
  - Germany Deutscher Akaemischer Austtauschdienst Correspondence 1958-1959 (Reel 26, Side 2, Index 29), Reel 26, Side 2, Index 29 (Reel 26)
  - Germany Deutcher Akademischer Austauschdienst Correspondence 1956-1957 (Reel 26, Side 2, Index 17), Reel 26, Side 2, Index 17 (Reel 26)
  - Germany Inactive Foreign Study Award D.A.A. Engineering Scholarships - Open to all the World 1955-1956 (Reel 26, Side 2, Index 13), Reel 26, Side 2, Index 13 (Reel 26)
  - Germany Deutscher Akademischer Austauschtdienst Correspondence 1953-1956 (Reel 26, Side 2, Index 16), Reel 26, Side 2, Index 16 (Reel 26)
  - Germany HICOG Dr. Ralph Burns 1950 (Reel 19, Side 1, Index 34), Reel 19, Side 1, Index 34 (Reel 19)
  - Germany 1950 (Reel 19, Side 1, Index 30), Reel 19, Side 1, Index 30 (Reel 19)
  - Germany Department of State Mr. James A. Donovan 1950 (Reel 19, Side 1, Index 25), Reel 19, Side 1, Index 25 (Reel 19)
  - Germany Department of State Lists of Sudents and Telegrams 1950 (Reel 19, Side 1, Index 26), Reel 19, Side 1, Index 26 (Reel 19)
  - Germany German Orientation Program 1950 (Reel 19, Side 1, Index 28), Reel 19, Side 1, Index 28 (Reel 19)
  - Germany Filled out Memo Sent by Exchanges for Budget Figuring 1950 (Reel 19, Side 1, Index 39), Reel 19, Side 1, Index 39 (Reel 19)
  - Germany General - Budget - Increased cost items not estimated 1950 (Reel 19, Side 1, Index 40), Reel 19, Side 1, Index 40 (Reel 19)
  - Germany German Lawyers 1950 (Reel 19, Side 1, Index 35), Reel 19, Side 1, Index 35 (Reel 19)
  - Germany IIE Policy Re Students 1950-1951 (Reel 19, Side 1, Index 43), Reel 19, Side 1, Index 43 (Reel 19)
  - Germany Bavarian Ministry of Education 1950-1954 (Reel 26, Side 2, Index 19), Reel 26, Side 2, Index 19 (Reel 26)
  - Germany Inactive Foreign Study Files Alex. Von Humboldt Award BadischeAnilin - Und - Soda Awards University of Gottingen 1950-1955 (Reel 26, Side 2, Index 10), Reel 26, Side 2, Index 10 (Reel 26)
  - Germany - General Student Exchange Publicity, Announcements 1950-1960 (Reel 26, Side 2, Index 23), Reel 26, Side 2, Index 23 (Reel 26)
  - Germany Visa and Immigration Information 1951 (Reel 19, Side 1, Index 41), Reel 19, Side 1, Index 41 (Reel 19)
  - Germany Colgate Plan for German Students 1951 (Reel 19, Side 1, Index 27), Reel 19, Side 1, Index 27 (Reel 19)
  - Germany Inactive Foreign Study Awards Leibnitz Kolleg and University of Tubingen 1951-1954-1955 (Reel 26, Side 2, Index 12), Reel 26, Side 2, Index 12 (Reel 26)
  - Germany General - Student Exchange Miscellaneous Correspondence 1960 Memos to Regional Offices 1951-1960 (Reel 26, Side 2, Index 28), Reel 26, Side 2, Index 28 (Reel 26)
  - Germany Free University of Berlin History and Correspondence 1952-1961 (Reel 26, Side 2, Index 25), Reel 26, Side 2, Index 25 (Reel 26)
  - Germany Inactive Foreign Study Award University of Kiel 1953-1955 (Reel 26, Side 2, Index 11), Reel 26, Side 2, Index 11 (Reel 26)
  - Germany Aachen Technische Hochschule Inactive Foreign Study Award Correspondence 1953-1959 (Reel 26, Side 2, Index 14), Reel 26, Side 2, Index 14 (Reel 26)
  - Germany Bavarian State Awards History and Correspondence 1955-1960 (Reel 26, Side 2, Index 20), Reel 26, Side 2, Index 20 (Reel 26)
  - Germany Wyomissing Foundation Grants 1956 (Reel 26, Side 2, Index 27), Reel 26, Side 2, Index 27 (Reel 26)
  - Germany - Fullbright U.S. Educational Commission Correspondence 1956-1957, 1956 (Reel 33, Side 2, Index 23), Reel 33, Side 2, Index 23 (Reel 33)
  - Germany Department of State (IES) Correspondence 1956-1957 1956 (Reel 33, Side 2, Index 24), Reel 33, Side 2, Index 24 (Reel 33)
  - Germany Miscellaneous Correspondence 1956-1957 1956 (Reel 33, Side 2, Index 25), Reel 33, Side 2, Index 25 (Reel 33)
  - Germany Selection Committee Correspondence and Lists of Members 1955-1961 (Reel 26, Side 2, Index 21), Reel 26, Side 2, Index 21 (Reel 26)
  - Germany - General IIE Papers on German American Exchanges 1959 (Reel 26, Side 2, Index 24), Reel 26, Side 2, Index 24 (Reel 26)
  - Education Germany 1927-1939 (Reel 6, Side 1, Index 4), Reel 6, Side 1, Index 4 (Reel 6)
  - Education Germany Foreign Students 1927-1941 (Reel 6, Side 1, Index 1), Reel 6, Side 1, Index 1 (Reel 6)
  - Education Germany Schools for Social Workers (Reel 6, Side 1, Index 10), Reel 6, Side 1, Index 10 (Reel 6)
  - Education Germany Schools for Girls 1928-1938 (Reel 6, Side 1, Index 2), Reel 6, Side 1, Index 2 (Reel 6)
  - Education Germany Foreign Students Other Universities 1928-1947 (Reel 6, Side 1, Index 11), Reel 6, Side 1, Index 11 (Reel 6)
  - Education Germany Schools- Coeducational 1930-1939 (Reel 6, Side 1, Index 9), Reel 6, Side 1, Index 9 (Reel 6)
  - Education Germany Foreign Students Berlin 1932-1937 (Reel 6, Side 1, Index 6), Reel 6, Side 1, Index 6 (Reel 6)
  - Education Germany Vocational 1932-1937 (Reel 6, Side 1, Index 3), Reel 6, Side 1, Index 3 (Reel 6)
  - Education Germany School for Boys 1932-1937 (Reel 6, Side 1, Index 8), Reel 6, Side 1, Index 8 (Reel 6)
  - Education Germany Higher Education-Before 1933 (Reel 6, Side 1, Index 13), Reel 6, Side 1, Index 13 (Reel 6)
  - Education Germany Higher - Handbooks - Dr. Herbert Schroeder 1933 (Reel 6, Side 1, Index 14), Reel 6, Side 1, Index 14 (Reel 6)
  - Education Germany Higher Hitler Regime Articles Clippings 1933 (Reel 5, Side 2, Index 10), Reel 5, Side 2, Index 10 (Reel 5)